[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to my post.
So friends, I will first take you to the news coming in about ICICI Bank
and I will try to tell you what the news is.
I have brought you to the Economic Times.
Friends, here you can see,
I am scrolling up a bit. Here
you can see that ICICI Bank board
to meet on July 8 to decide on fund raise. So,
a board meeting is going to be held in ICICI Bank on July
8 regarding fund raising. So,
why do you want to do fund raising and
how much will be the fund raising, we will
know all this in detail by reading the news. And
here you can see that private
lender ICICI Bank on Sunday said that its
board meeting will on July 8 consider raising
funds through an equity share sale as it looks for further
strength in its balance
sheet. To give further strength to its balance sheet, to
strengthen the balance sheet, it
wants to raise funds so that it can
grow its business. Before this,
three other big banks of India have raised funds. Kotak
mahindrafinance.com
billion  They can raise funds in dollars.
It has informed the exchange in a notice that
it is going to raise funds in various ways to
strengthen its balance sheet.
As I told you, if we
move ahead, friends, it had already generated Rs 3090 crore by
selling a little of its stake in ICICI Prudential and ICICI Lord General Insurance
and the
rest was done one by one here.
Here we can see that the private
lender had also taken a separate and
enabling solution in the month of May to raise Rs
25000 crore from there. It had also deposited Rs 25000 crore from there as well as through dep
security. Here,
it is planning to raise $3 billion. So
friends, this is very good
news for ICICI Bank if the
banks get money. However,
you must be aware of all these banks that yes, first Axis
Bank, then Kotak Mahindra, then HDFC and
now ICICI Bank, why are all these trying to raise new money?
You must be aware
that due to Covid-19, all the banks are at
risk.  There is a provisioning
issue and keeping that in mind,
because that money is going to get locked there, so
if the banks' money gets locked then they will
not be able to give loans in future and if they are
not able to give loans further then their profitability will decrease. So to
handle all this, they are
raising new money so that if their
NPS problem increases in the coming days,
which is going to increase, then they
can again take their business forward with the new money. So
friends, this is good news. I think
you should put AAA Bank on your watch list
because as soon as
this news progresses on July 8,
I definitely see the possibility of it remaining bullish. So once
we will look at the chart and
try to know what levels are coming,
friends, I have brought you to the chart,
here you can see that
around January-February 2020, ICICI
Bank was making a high around 500-50, it
tried to touch 50 many times, one
here friends, you can see it was here
also, it was tried here also.  After that, it happened
here as well, and after that, a nose-
dry fall occurred, friends, due to the COVID-19 issue. By
March 24th, a low of ₹68 was
formed. After that, there was a good recovery. It went
around 380 once, then
declined again. After that, it went to the
level of around 380. There was another
fall between 380 and 390.
After that, it tried to touch the 380 level once again, then it
declined again. And as of now, on
June 24th, it tried to reach around 380
and declined again.
After June 3rd, if we talk about July 3rd, friends,
then its closing was 361, which means that it is
currently seen trading around the resistance level. So,
friends, you should
not rush into taking a position here at all.
However, here you can see that
after it made a low of 3268, the trend
line  It also appears to be following this trend, so it's
possible that the market will see a slight correction
because the market has already run high. So, if there's a
chance that the
market will correct, then ICICI Bank will
also see a correction. At the most,
I see a level around 290 here,
although I do
n't see a chance of it falling that much right now. Its first
support level is 320, and after that, if we
talk about the trend line,
it could get support at a level around 300. But if
this fund raises due to fund raising
and it manages to
successfully close above 390,
then friends, there's full hope of further upside.
If it breaks the 390 level,
I see another level here,
friends, it
could go around 450. So, friends, you
can add ICICI Bank to your list and
keep an eye on the levels and targets as I discussed. Once we
go to NSC,
what was the last trading detail?  If you try to find out during the trading day, then
friends, you can see that
I have searched for Aaa Bank here. The
last closing price was ₹360.8 p. There was a
decline of 0.5 p. Once we can
also see how the deliveries were, the quantity
traded was 2 crore 7779 331 shares, in
which 642258 shares were delivered. There was a
delivery of 22 p. So friends, the
deliveries here seem to be going well.
However, if you look at a normal day, such
banks have good deliveries, they are always around 50 p.m.
But
in the last trading day, there was a delivery of around 22 p.m. So, there is
no need to rush into taking a position at the moment,
friends. If it closes above 390 and
sustains, then only you should take a
position at the higher level with a stop loss of 380.
Or if it comes down a little, then
you can think of taking a position around the 300 level.
I can see a strong support level here, so
friends, if you liked this video then please
like it and if you are
new to my channel then definitely subscribe.
Thank you again for watching this video
[Music]